// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q021: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Those who do not return their rental cars by the scheduled due date will be charged an ------ fee.',
      choices: ['addition', 'additionally', 'add', 'additional'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['additional'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題201-210/#q201',
    },
    {
      question: 'The marketing director told department staff that more emphasis should be placed ------ advertising through social media.',
      choices: ['from', 'on', 'into', 'of'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['on'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題201-210/#q202',
    },
    {
      question: 'Of the ten accounting assistant candidates, three were invited to interview with the accounting manager ------ the first round of interviews.',
      choices: ['now that', 'even though', 'so that', 'after'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['after'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題201-210/#q203',
    },
    {
      question: 'Tablet sales are going ------ well this quarter that we have to decide whether to increase the number of workers in our production department.',
      choices: ['very', 'such', 'so', 'quite'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['so'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題201-210/#q204',
    },
    {
      question: 'Ms. Hollander toured more than 20 properties before making the ------ decision to purchase the house.',
      choices: ['final', 'finally', 'finalize', 'finalizes'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['final'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題201-210/#q205',
    },
    {
      question: 'The system is currently undergoing maintenance, so you are ------ unable to log in to the member page.',
      choices: ['slightly', 'commonly', 'overwhelmingly', 'temporarily'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['temporarily'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題201-210/#q206',
    },
    {
      question: 'The CEO explained to the employees that protecting customers’ personal information is a very ------ priority.',
      choices: ['height', 'high', 'highly', 'heighten'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['high'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題201-210/#q207',
    },
    {
      question: 'The September concert by a renowned jazz pianist is very popular and should be booked ------ in advance.',
      choices: ['much', 'very', 'still', 'well'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['well'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題201-210/#q208',
    },
    {
      question: 'At James Fitness Gym, free yoga classes every Saturday afternoon are ------ available to members.',
      choices: ['exclude', 'exclusive', 'exclusively', 'exclusion'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['exclusively'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題201-210/#q209',
    },
    {
      question: 'The restaurant on the top floor of the Anshelt Hotel offers a spectacular night view and an ------ dining experience.',
      choices: ['aspiring', 'exhausted', 'exceptional', 'applicable'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['exceptional'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題201-210/#q210',
    },
  ],
}